Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1989.0080
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series V: Legislative Files, undated, 1949-1989
  - Subseries M: Subject Files, undated, 1952-1991
    - Minimum wage, 1977, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2304-2305)
    - Northeast AFL-CIO Council, 1987 (Box 191)
    - O'Neill, William (Governor), 1986 (Box 182)
    - Other state federations, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Platform hearings, CSLC, 1974 (Box 60:, Folder 2306)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, undated (Box 203)
    - Public Acts, 1987 (Box 182)
    - Public employees department ( AFL-CIO), 1977 (Box 60:, Folder 2307)
    - Public Employee Department Conference, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Public works, 1975-1977 (Box 60:, Folder 2308-2309)
    - Reception for new legislators, 1991 (Box 203)
    - Regional Conference, New York City, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Resolutions, 1971 (Box 60:, Folder 2310)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, undated (Box 60)
      - Legislative releases, 1973 (Box 60:, Folder 2311)
      - Voting record, 1961-1962 (Box 60:, Folder 2312)
    - Secretary of the State, undated (Box 203)
    - Select testimony against “Right to Work” bill, 1952 (Box 60:, Folder 2313)
    - Senate, 1986 (Box 182)
    - Social Security, CSLC platform proposals, 1958 (Box 60:, Folder 2314)
    - State Board of Mediation and Arbitration, 1980 (Box 60:, Folder 2315)
    - State Central Bodies meeting, Meany Center, 1986 (Box 191)
    - State Council pamphlets, 1965 (Box 60:, Folder 2316)
    - State Employees Association, 1978 (Box 60:, Folder 2317)
    - State employer pay fight, 1975 (Box 60:, Folder 2318)
    - State Ethics Commission, lobbying information, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2319)
    - State treasurer, undated (Box 203)
    - Summer school of union women, Storrs, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Sunday blue laws, undated (Box 60:, Folder 2320)
    - TASC, undated (Box 143)
    - Task force report on construction projects, 1972 (Box 60:, Folder 2321)
    - Technology Transfer Conference, 1979 (Box 60:, Folder 2322)
    - Teleconference on organizing, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Trip to Zimbabwe, Zaire, Cote D'Ivoire, Ghana, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Unemployment, undated (Box 60)
      - General, 1972-1977 (Box 60:, Folder 2323-2329)
      - Press clippings, 1970-1980 (Box 60:, Folder 2330)
      - Strike compensation, 1969-1970 (Box 60:, Folder 2331)
    - United States congresspeople, undated (Box 203)
    - United States government issues, undated (Box 203)
    - United States senators, undated (Box 203)
    - Urban Coalition of Bridgeport, 1969-1970 (Box 60:, Folder 2332-2333)
    - Weicker, Lowell, undated (Box 143)
    - Wiecker, Lowell P., Governor (Box 203)
    - Workers Memorial Day, 1989; (2 fl) (Box 191)
    - Workmen's Compensation Law, 1960-1973 (Box 60:, Folder 2334)
    - Youth employment, 1963 (Box 60:, Folder 2335)
    - Young Unionist Action League, 1970-1975 (Box 60:, Folder 2336)
  - Subseries N: U.S. Government, undated, 1980-1989
    - Bush, undated (Box 196)
    - Collective bargaining for state employees, 1986 (Box 183)
    - Congressional questionnaire, 1986 (Box 183)
    - COPE meeting, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Convention miscellany, 1986 (Box 182)
    - Crisis and Opportunity for Labor, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Economic Conference, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Fourth District Special Election, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Governor's Task Force on Toxic Chemical Release, 1986 (Box 183)
    - House
      - General, 1983-1984 (Box 132:, Folder 3802)
      - William Cotter, 1981-1982 (Box 132:, Folder 3803)
      - Larry DeNordis, 1981-1982 (Box 132:, Folder 3804)
      - Sam Gejdenson, 1981-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3805-3806)
      - Nancy Johnson, 1982-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3807-3808)
      - Barbara Kennelly, 1982-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3809)
      - Stuart McKinney, 1982-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3810-3813)
      - McKinney, Stuart>, 1986 (Box 182)
      - Bruce Morrison, 1982-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3814-3816)
      - Toby Moffet, 1980-1982 (Box 132:, Folder 3817)
      - Moffett, Toby, 1985 (Box 182)
      - Moffett, Toby, undated (Box 196)
      - William Ratchford, 1981-1982 (Box 132:, Folder 3818)
      - John Rowland, 1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3819)
    - Impasse resolution, 1986 (Box 183)
    - Joint Labor-Management and Health Care Costs Containment Committee, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Legislative Bulletin, 1985-1987; (3 fl) (Box 182)
    - Legislative Conference, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Legislative session, 1987 (Box 183)
    - MacBride principles, undated (Box 183)
    - Major bills, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Members of Congress, 1987 (Box 183)
    - National Legislative Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 183)
    - Senate
      - Christopher Dodd, 1980-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3793-3797)
      - Lowell Weicker, 1980-1985 (Box 132:, Folder 3798-3801)
      - Weicker, Lowell, 1988 (Box 182)
      - Weicker, Lowell, 1989 (Box 183)
    - Tuft Seminar, undated (Box 183)
    - U.S.-Canada Free Trade Agreement, 1988 (Box 183)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Workers Compensation Conference, 1987 (Box 183)
- Series VI: Convention Materials, undated, 1921-1985
  - Subseries A: Proceedings, 1921-1985
    Scope and Contents note
    [see also Tianti files]
    - CT State Industrial Union Council Conventions (Box 61)
      - 1st, 1938 November 13 - 14 (Box 61:, Folder 2337)
      - 2nd, 1939 October 28 - 29 (Box 61:, Folder 2338)
      - 3rd, 1940 October 26 - 27 (Box 61:, Folder 2339)
      - 5th, 1943 January 13 - 14 (Box 61:, Folder 2340)
      - 6th, 1943 December 3 - 5 (Box 61:, Folder 2341-2344)
      - 7th, 1944 November 18 - 19 (Box 61:, Folder 2345)
      - 8th, 1945 November 17 - 18 (Box 61:, Folder 2346)
      - 9th, 1946 December 7 - 8 (Box 61:, Folder 2347-2348)
      - 10th, 1947 December 6 - 7 (Box 61:, Folder 2349)
      - 11th, 1949 January 15 - 16 (Box 61:, Folder 2350-2351)
      - 12th, 1950 January 13 - 15 (Box 61:, Folder 2352-2354)
      - 13th, 1951 January 13 - 14 (Box 61:, Folder 2355)
      - 14th, 1952 January 12 - 13 (Box 62:, Folder 2356)
      - 15th, 1953 January 23 - 25 (Box 62:, Folder 2357)
      - 16th, 1954 January 15 - 17 (Box 62:, Folder 2358)
      - 17th, 1955 January 14 - 16 (Box 62:, Folder 2359-2362)
      - 18th, 1956 January 20 - 22 (Box 62:, Folder 2363-2364)
      - 19th, 1957 January 18 - 19 (Box 62:, Folder 2365-2366)
      - Special Merger Convention, 1957 June 11 - 12 (Box 62:, Folder 2367)
    - CT Federation of Labor Conventions
      - 36th, 1921 June 6 - 9 (Box 62:, Folder 2368)
      - 42nd, 1927 September 7 - 9 (Box 62:, Folder 2369)
      - 43rd, 1928 September 4 - 7 (Box 62:, Folder 2370)
      - 44th, 1929 September 3 - 6 (Box 62:, Folder 2371)
      - 46th, 1931 September 8 - 10 (Box 62:, Folder 2372)
      - 48th, 1933 September 5 - 7 (Box 62:, Folder 2373)
      - 49th, 1934 September 4 - 6 (Box 62:, Folder 2374)
      - 50th, 1935 September 3 - 6 (Box 62:, Folder 2375)
      - 51st, 1936 September 8 - 11 (Box 62:, Folder 2376)
      - 52nd, 1937 September 7 - 10 (Box 62:, Folder 2377)
      - 53rd, 1938 September 6 - 9 (Box 62:, Folder 2378)
      - 54th, 1939 September 5 - 8 (Box 62:, Folder 2379)
      - 55th, 1940 September 3 - 6 (Box 62:, Folder 2380)
      - 56th, 1941 September 2 - 5 (Box 62:, Folder 2381)
      - 57th - 63rd, 1942-1948 (Box 62:, Folder 2382)
      - 61st, 1946 September 3 - 6 (Box 62:, Folder 2383)
      - 64th, 1949 September 20 - 23 (Box 62:, Folder 2384)
      - 67th, 1952 September 2 - 5 (Box 62:, Folder 2385-2386)
      - 68th, 1953 September 1 - 4 (Box 62:, Folder 2387-2389)
      - 69th, 1954 October 12 - 15 (Box 62:, Folder 2390-2392)
      - 70th, 1955 September 13 - 16 (Box 62:, Folder 2393-2394)
      - 71st, 1956 September 25 - 28 (Box 62:, Folder 2395-2397)
      - 72nd, 1957 June 10 - 13 (Box 62:, Folder 2398-2399)
      - Special Convention, 1957 June 12 (Box 62:, Folder 2400)
    - CT State Labor Council Conventions
      - 1st, 1957 June 13 (Box 64:, Folder 2401-2402)
      - 2nd, 1958 September 8 - 10 (Box 64:, Folder 2403)
      - 3rd, 1959 September 10 - 12 (Box 65:, Folder 2404-2407)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1960 August 29 - 31 (Box 65:, Folder 2408-2414)
      - 4th, 1961 August 6 - 8 (Box 65:, Folder 2415-2418)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1962 September 5 - 7 (Box 65:, Folder 2419-2426)
      - 5th, 1963 September 4 - 6 (Box 65:, Folder 2427-2431)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1964 September 9 - 11 (Box 66:, Folder 2432-2437)
      - 6th, 1965 September 15 - 17 (Box 66:, Folder 2438-2443)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1966 September 7 - 9 (Box 66:, Folder 2444)
      - 7th, 1967 September 15 - 17 (Box 67:, Folder 2445-2446)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1968 September 11 - 13 (Box 67:, Folder 2447-2452)
      - 8th, 1969 February 7, September 3 - 5 (Box 67:, Folder 2453-2458)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1970 September 9 - 11 (Box 67:, Folder 2459-2461)
      - 9th, 1971 September 15 - 17 (Box 68:, Folder 2462-2465)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1972 September 28 - 30 (Box 68:, Folder 2466)
      - 10th Constitutional, 1973 September 24 - 26 (Box 68:, Folder 2467)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1974 September 19 - 21 (Box 68:, Folder 2468-2471)
      - 11th, 1975 September 10 - 11 (Box 68:, Folder 2472-2474)
      - 20th, 1976 September 22 (Box 68:, Folder 2475)
      - 20th Constitutional, 1976 September 24 (Box 68:, Folder 2476)
      - 21st, 1977 September 28 - 30 (Box 68:, Folder 2477-2483)
      - 22nd, 1978 September 20 (Box 68:, Folder 2484)
      - 23rd, 1979 September 12 - 14 (Box 68:, Folder 2485-2488)
      - 24th, 1980 August 26 (Box 68:, Folder 2489)
      - 25th, 1981 September 14 (Box 68:, Folder 2490)
      - 26th, 1982 September 22 - 24 (Box 68:, Folder 2491)
      - 27th, 1983 (Box 68:, Folder 2492)
      - 28th, 1984 September 19 (Box 68:, Folder 2493)
      - 29th, 1985 September 12 (Box 68:, Folder 2494)
    - American Federation of Labor Convention (AFL-National) (Box 69)
      - 44th-46th, 1924-1926 (Box 69:, Folder 2495)
      - 47th-49th, 1927-1929 (Box 69:, Folder 2496)
      - 51st, 1931 (Box 69:, Folder 2497)
      - 54th, 1934 (Box 69:, Folder 2498)
      - 55th, 1935 (Box 69:, Folder 2499)
      - 56th, 1936 (Box 69:, Folder 2500)
      - 57th, 1937 (Box 69:, Folder 2501)
      - 58th, 1938 (Box 69:, Folder 2502)
      - 59th [marked “49”], 1939 (Box 70:, Folder 2503)
      - 60th, 1940 (Box 70:, Folder 2504)
      - 61st, 1941 (Box 70:, Folder 2505)
      - 62nd, 1942 (Box 70:, Folder 2506)
      - 63rd, 1943 (Box 70:, Folder 2507)
      - 64th, 1944 (Box 70:, Folder 2508)
      - 65th, 1946 (Box 70:, Folder 2509)
      - 66th, 1947 (Box 70:, Folder 2510)
      - 67th, 1948 (Box 70:, Folder 2511)
    - AFL-CIO Constitutional Conventions
      - 1st, 1955 (Box 70:, Folder 2512)
      - 2nd, 1957 (Box 71:, Folder 2513)
      - 3rd, 1959 (Box 71:, Folder 2514)
      - 4th, 1961 (Box 71:, Folder 2515)
      - 5th, 1963 (Box 71:, Folder 2516)
    - Verbatim proceedings, undated (Box 144)
    - Verbatim proceedings, undated (Box 145)
    - Verbatim Proceedings, 13th Annual, 1986 (Box 173)
    - Convention, 1985 (Box 173)
  - Subseries B: Convention Books, undated, 1928-1941
    - CT Federation of Labor Annual Conventions
      - 43rd, 1928 (Box 71:, Folder 2517)
      - 44th, 1929 (Box 71:, Folder 2518)
      - 45th, 1930 (Box 71:, Folder 2519)
      - 46th-56th, 1931-1941 (Box 71:, Folder 2520)
    - Convention resolution booklets, undated (Box 146)
  - Subseries C: Convention Reports, 1924-1983
    - CT State Industrial Union Council
      - President's reports, 1947-1957 (Box 71:, Folder 2521)
      - Secretary-Treasurer's reports, 1943-1957 (Box 71:, Folder 2522)
      - Legislative reports, 1950-1957 (Box 72:, Folder 2523)
      - Annual convention results, 1955, 1957 (Box 72:, Folder 2524)
        - 12th, 1950 January 13 - 15 (Box 72:, Folder 2525)
        - 13th, 1951 January 13 - 14 (Box 72:, Folder 2526)
        - 14th, 1952 January 12 - 13 (Box 72:, Folder 2527)
        - 16th, 1954 January 15 - 17 (Box 72:, Folder 2528)
        - 17th, 1955 January 14 - 16 (Box 72:, Folder 2529)
        - 18th, 1956 January 20-22 (Box 72:, Folder 2530)
        - 19th, 1957 January 18 - 19 (Box 72:, Folder 2531)
      - Merger Convention, 1957 June 13 (Box 72:, Folder 2532)
    - Connecticut Federation of Labor Conventions
      - 39th, 1924 September 2 (Box 72:, Folder 2533)
      - 66th, 1951 September 11 - 15 (Box 72:, Folder 2534)
      - 70th, 1954 September 13 - 16 (Box 72:, Folder 2535)
    - Connecticut State Labor Council AFL-CIO
      - 2nd September, 1958 8 - 10 (Box 72:, Folder 2536)
      - 3rd, 1959 September 10 - 12 (Box 72:, Folder 2537)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1960 August 29 - 31 (Box 72:, Folder 2538)
      - 4th, 1961 September 6 - 8 (Box 72:, Folder 2539)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1962 September 5 - 7 (Box 72:, Folder 2540)
      - 5th, 1963 September 4 - 6 (Box 72:, Folder 2541)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1964 September 9 - 11 (Box 72:, Folder 2542)
      - 6th, 1965 September 15 - 17 (Box 72:, Folder 2543)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1966 September 7 - 9 (Box 72:, Folder 2544)
      - 7th, 1967 September 13 - 15 (Box 72:, Folder 2545)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1968 September 11 - 13 (Box 72:, Folder 2546)
      - 8th, 1969 September 3 - 5 (Box 72:, Folder 2547)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1970 September 9 - 11 (Box 72:, Folder 2548)
      - 9th, 1971 September 15 - 17 (Box 72:, Folder 2549)
      - Legislative, Political Educational, 1972 September 28 - 30 (Box 72:, Folder 2550)
      - 10th, 1973 September 24 - 26 (Box 72:, Folder 2551)
      - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1974 September 19 - 21 (Box 72:, Folder 2552)
      - 11th Constitutional, 1975 September 10 - 12 (Box 73:, Folder 2553)
      - 20th, 1976 September 22 - 24 (Box 73:, Folder 2554)
      - 21st, 1977 September 28 - 30 (Box 73:, Folder 2555)
      - 22nd, 1978 September 20 - 22 (Box 73:, Folder 2556)
      - 23rd, 1979 September 12 - 14 (Box 73:, Folder 2557)
      - 25th, 1981 September 14 - 16 (Box 73:, Folder 2558)
      - 26th, 1982 September 22 - 24 (Box 73:, Folder 2559)
      - 27th, 1983 September 21 - 23 (Box 73:, Folder 2560)
  - Subseries D: Roll Call Lists, 1957-1969
    - Special Merger, 1957 (Box 73:, Folder 2561)
    - 2nd Annual Convention, 1958 (Box 73:, Folder 2562)
    - 3rd Annual Convention, 1959 (Box 73:, Folder 2563)
    - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1960 (Box 73:, Folder 2564)
    - 4th Constitutional, 1961 (Box 73:, Folder 2565)
    - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1962 (Box 73:, Folder 2566)
    - 5th Constitutional, 1963 (Box 73:, Folder 2567)
    - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1964 (Box 73:, Folder 2568)
    - 6th Constitutional, 1965 (Box 73:, Folder 2569)
    - Legislative, Political & Educational, 1966 (Box 73:, Folder 2670)
    - 8th Constitutional, 1969 (Box 73:, Folder 2671)
  - Subseries E: Correspondence, undated, 1950-1957
    - CT State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1953 (Box 73:, Folder 2672-2674)
    - Merger Convention, 1957 (Box 73:, Folder 2675-2682)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2683)
      - Proposed rules, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2684)
      - Notes, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2685)
      - Resolutions, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2686)
      - Roll Call, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2687)
      - Minutes of Merger Committee, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2688)
      - Auditor's report—CIO, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2689)
    - Union membership, undated (Box 73:, Folder 2690)
    - CT Federation of Labor Conventions, 1954-1957 (Box 73:, Folder 2691-2703)
    - American Federation of Labor, 1951-1955 (Box 73:, Folder 2704)
  - Subseries F: Committees, undated, 1982-1991
    - 1982 Convention, undated (Box 147)
      - Union Label Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Credentials Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Arrangements Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Resolutions Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Constitutional Amendment, undated (Box 147)
      - Education Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Rules Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Materials ordered for Kitz, undated (Box 147)
      - Reports, undated (Box 147)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 147)
    - 1983 Convention, undated (Box 147)
      - Constitutional Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Education Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Rules Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Convention, undated (Box 147)
      - Community Services Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Credentials Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Arrangements Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Resolutions Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Presidential contest, undated (Box 147)
      - Materials ordered for Kitz, undated (Box 147)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 147)
    - 1984 Convention, undated (Box 147)
      - Conventions, undated (Box 147)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 147)
      - Legislative Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Education Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Community Services Committee, undated (Box 147)
      - Speakers and invitations, undated (Box 147)
      - Materials ordered for Kitz, undated (Box 147)
      - Resolutions Committee, undated (Box 147)
    - 1991 Convention (Box 203)
      - 35th Annual Convention of the Connecticut State, undated (Box 203)
      - AFL/CIO, 1991
      - Arrangement Committee, undated (Box 203)
      - Affiliates list, undated (Box 203)
      - C.L.C. vice presidents, undated (Box 203)
      - Community Services Committee (Box 203)
      - Constitution of the Connecticut State AFL/CIO, 1991 (Box 203)
      - Constitutional amendments, undated (Box 203)
      - Constitution Committee, undated (Box 203)
      - Credentials Committee, undated (Box 203)
      - Convention greetings, undated (Box 203)
      - Display tables, undated (Box 203)
      - Education Committee, undated (Box 203)
      - Executive Board nominees and candidates, undated (Box 203)
      - Hartford Convention and Visitors Bureau, undated (Box 203)
      - “Labor News”, 1994 (Box 203)
      - Legislative Committee, undated (Box 203)
      - Materials for printers, undated (Box 203)
      - Materials ordered for kits, undated (Box 203)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 203)
      - Per capita strength, undated (Box 203)
      - Presidential campaign, undated (Box 203)
      - Resolutions Committee, undated (Box 203)
      - Resolutions submitted to the 33rd Annual Convention of the Connecticut State AFL/CIO, 1989-91; (2 folders) (Box 203)
      - Speakers, biographies of, undated (Box 203)
      - Speakers and invitations, undated (Box 203)
      - Women's and Civil Rights breakfast, undated (Box 203)
  - 1993-1994 Convention, 1992-1994
    - Notes, correspondence, fliers, administrative records, legal documents, 1992-1993 (Box 205)
      [Subjects include: leadership, conferences/meetings, workers' compensation, ergonomics, Bridgeport Financial Review, Department of Labor, prison work, injured workers' forum, United Way, women in government, senators, representatives, U.S. Congress]
    - Correspondence, notes, administrative records, fliers, awards, transcripts, 1994 (Box 206)
      [Subjects include: speakers, invitations, biographies, Legislative committee, Rally for Health Care, Lobbyist workshop, NE Council Public Employees Conference, material for printer, COPE Committee, COPE Executive Board Members, Central Labor Councils]
    - Correspondence, fliers, notes, administrative records, clippings, 1993 (Box 207)
      [Subjects include: CLC Presidents Committee, COPE Workshop, Round 2 of VIP Meetings, Health Care Committee, United Labor Agency, National AFL-CIO Community Services, Workers' comp Advisory Committee, Tammy MacFadyen, Dept. of Economic Research, Union Benefits Program.]
    - Publications, correspondence, administrative records, notes (Box 208)
      [Subjects include: Escort, arrangement, community service, credentials, resolution, rules, education, and legislative committees, per capita strength, CLC Vice Presidents, suites and third floor map, Women's and Civil Rights breakfast, Presidential Campaign.]
- Series VII: Printed Materials and Publications, undated, 1909-1986
  - Subseries A: Publications, 1909-1986
    - CT State Industrial Union Council (CIO), undated (Box 73:, Folder 2705)
    - Constitutions, 1943-1947 (Box 74:, Folder 2706-2707)
    - Yearbooks, 1950-1957 (Box 74:, Folder 2708-2716)
    - CT State Industrial Union yearbook, 1957 (Box 186)
    - CT State Labor Council AFL-CIO Second Official yearbook, 1958-1959 (Box 186)
    - Vanguard
      (see also Boxes 77-78 for oversize)
      - 1941 December (Box 186:, Folder 2717)
      - 1945 May - December (Box 186:, Folder 2718)
      - 1946 January - December (Box 186:, Folder 2719)
      - 1950 January - April, June - November (Box 186:, Folder 2720)
      - 1951 January - December (Box 186:, Folder 2721)
      - 1953 January - April, June - December (Box 186:, Folder 2722)
      - 1954 January - December (Box 186:, Folder 2723)
      - 1955 January - December (Box 186:, Folder 2724)
      - 1956 January - December (Box 186:, Folder 2725)
      - 1957 February - May, August - November (Box 186:, Folder 2726)
      - 1958 January - December (Box 186:, Folder 2727)
    - Connecticut Federation of Labor (AFL)
      - AFL Constitution (national), 1952 (Box 186:, Folder 2728)
      - CFL Constitution (AFL), 1951-1956 (Box 186:, Folder 2729)
      - CFL Constitution (AFL-CIO), 1956 (Box 186:, Folder 2730)
      - Official Journal and Directory, 1923-1926 (Box 186:, Folder 2731-2734)
      - CFL bulletin, 1948-1955 (Box 186:, Folder 2735-2737)
      - CFL Legislative bulletin, 1953 (Box 186:, Folder 2738)
      - CFL and CSIUC legislative bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 186:, Folder 2739)
      - CFL legal bulletin, 1952-1957 (Box 186:, Folder 2740-2743)
      - CFL yearbook, 1932 (Box 186:, Folder 2744)
      - CFL, Connecticut Federationist, 1939-1956 (Box 186:, Folder 2745-2757)
    - Connecticut State Labor Council AFL-CIO
      - AFL-CIO (national)—constitution draft, 1955 (Box 186:, Folder 2758)
      - AFL-CIO (national)—constitution draft, 1955 (Box 75:, Folder 2759)
      - AFL-CIO (national)—Constitution, 1956 (Box 75:, Folder 2760)
      - CSLC
        - Constitution, 1971-1983 (Box 75:, Folder 2761-2767)
        - News, 1960-1976 (Box 75:, Folder 2768)
        - Yearbooks, 1957-1959 (Box 75:, Folder 2769-2770)
        - Labor notes and quotes, 1962-1965 (Box 75:, Folder 2771)
        - Legislative bulletin, 1971-1980 (Box 75:, Folder 2772)
      - Newspapers/Correspondence
        - Vanguard, 1970-1972 (Box 76:, Folder 2773-2777)
        - Call to Action, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2778-2780)
        - AFL-CIO News, 1977-1986 (Box 76:, Folder 2781)
      - Vanguard (Box 77)
        - 1941-1949
        - 1950-1952 (Box 77a)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 78)
        - 1956-1958 (Box 78a)
      - AFL-CIO News, 1977-1982 (Box 78b)
      - Newsletter, 1962-1969 (Box 78c)
      - Call to Action, 1973-1977
      - Vanguard, 1970-1971
      - Connecticut Federation of Labor Bulletin, 1948-1949 (Box 78)
      - CFL, AFL Legal Bulletin, 1952-1953
      - CFL, AFL Legal Bulletin/Newsletter I, 1954-1955
      - CFL, AFL Legal Bulletin/Newsletter II, 1955-1956
      - CFL, AFL Legal Bulletin/Newsletter III, 1956-1957
    - Federationist, undated (Box 148)
    - Yearbook, undated (Box 148)
    - Vanguard, undated (Box 149-150)
    - AFL-CIO News, undated (Box 151)
    - Pamphlets, general, 1961-1962 (Box 152)
    - School kits, 1961-1976 (Box 153)
    - Labor agreements/constitution, 1945-1982 (Box 154)